http://www.frontierpharm.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Statement has been Created to Ensure that You Understand Our Corporate Policies...
Frontier Pharmaceutical, Inc. takes your privacy seriously and we want you to understand the ways in which we do and do not use the information that you transmit when you visit our website. This statement discloses the entire Corporate Privacy Practices for the https://www.FrontierPharm.com website. Further, we encourage you to read our Terms of Use statement as it contains information that is important to those who use our website.
Terms of Use
We also expect our website visitors to comply with our Terms of Use Statement. Please read these terms and conditions carefully. By accessing this website you agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions stated therein. They pertain to: Copyright, Trademark, Web Content and Materials, Links to Other Sites, Limitation of Liability, Enforceability and Governing Laws.
If after reading our Terms of Use statement, you still have questions, we encourage you to call us to obtain the answers you are seeking. Contact us for more details...
Privacy Statement
Data Collection and Usage We collect the following information about our users, which will be used by ourselves and our agents: click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, search terms, URI of requested resource, query-string portion of URI, request date, request time, other access log fields, user agent information, and navigation and click-stream data. This data will be used for the following purposes: completion and support of the current activity, Website and system administration, and research and development. We use non-personal information such as demographic data to analyze and develop our marketing strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our services and how to further improve our Website based upon user data. We do not sell or share any personal information gathered on the site with any third party.
Cookies Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Website. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used to track visitors to our site so we may better understand what portions of our site best serve you. Our Web server automatically collects some information about you when you request pages from our server, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. This information does not identify you personally.
Log Files We also collect IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personal information.
Legal Disclaimer We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on the Website.
Minors No portion of our services is directed towards minors (individuals below the age of 18) and we do not knowingly solicit any information about minors or market to minors.
Security Privacy is very important to Frontier Pharmaceutical, Inc. We take every precaution to protect our users' information. All information gathered on our https://www.FrontierPharm.com website is protected for storage within a controlled database. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
Notification of Changes Frontier Pharmaceutical, Inc. may change this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our site.
Business Relationships Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that Frontier Pharmaceutical, Inc. has no control or influence over the privacy practices of such other sites nor is it responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personal information.
Enforcements If users have any questions or complaints with respect to the principles outlined in this privacy statement or enforcement of this privacy statement they should contact:
Frontier Pharmaceutical, Inc. 10 Ponderosa Drive Melville, New York 11747 Toll Free: (800) 767-3486 Phone: (631) 367-3400 Fax: (631) 692-7642
To keep up to date with our news, events and campaigns.
follow us:
© 2019 Frontier Pharm, All rights reserved. | eCommerce website design by QeRetail
